Privacy Policy March 2018

Welcome to the web site of Energy Rewards, LLC (“Energy Rewards”). Energy Rewards respects the

privacy of individuals who use our web site. This Privacy Policy explains our online information practices

and is designed to assist you in making informed decisions while using our web site. Please note that by

visiting the Energy Rewards web site, you consent to the practices described below and agree to comply

with and be bound by the following Privacy Policy. Please read the Energy Rewards Privacy Policy

carefully and in its entirety. Please be aware that the privacy policy referenced at the bottom of the Web

page governs the collection of information on that page.

Information Collection and Usage

Energy Rewards is committed to protecting your personal information as you use our website. Energy

Rewards does not collect personally identifiable information from anyone unless such information

is provided to us voluntarily and knowingly except as otherwise provided in this Policy. We only

collect personal information for specific purposes, including providing you with retail energy services. We

will not sell or make available your personal information to unaffiliated companies for commercial

purposes unrelated to the business of Energy Rewards. However, we may use this information to

inform you of goods or services that may interest you. Energy Rewards will not disclose any information

about you to unaffiliated companies or organizations without your consent except as disclosed to you

in this Policy, unless: (a) we are required to do so by law; (b) we believe it necessary to respond to an

inquiry or provide you with a requested service; (c) it is necessary to make good on our Terms of Service

Agreement we have entered into with you; or (d) to protect the rights, property or personal safety

of any other person, including another Energy Rewards Customer or any member of the public.

Energy Rewards and its affiliates recognize that by utilizing our website you are placing trust in us. We

thank you. Let us assure you that we will take precautions to protect your information. In order to operate

the website and deliver retail energy service we may share your personal information with a service

partner under strict conditions. We will not otherwise disclose your personal information to other

companies without your explicit consent.

You are not required to register or provide information to us in order to view a large majority of our site.

However, to obtain services from Energy Rewards or to access portions of our website, including, but not

limited to, services provided by Energy Rewards, you may be asked to provide personal information. We

use your information to personalize your web experience or to provide you with requested services.

Energy Rewards will only use your information strictly in accordance with this Policy.

How We Protect Your Information

We maintain reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to restrict access to your

personally identifiable information to employees and personnel who need to know such information in

order to operate, develop or improve our services. Any such personal information is transferred to our

servers. Electronic safeguards include technology such as firewalls and Secure Sockets Layers (SSL) to

protect and encrypt certain sensitive transmissions of information. However, you should keep in mind

that this website is run on software, hardware, and networks, any component of which may, from time

to time, require maintenance, experience problems or breaches of security. You are solely responsible for

maintaining the confidentiality of any username and/or password and are responsible for any

unauthorized use.

Children's Privacy

Our website contains educational energy‐related information that may be of interest to children. Energy

Rewards does not seek to gather personal information online from or about children under the age of

18. Energy Rewards encourages all children and young teens to ask their parents for authorization

before providing any information about themselves or their household to anyone over the Internet.

Data Collection

Energy Rewards may use "cookie" technology on our website. "Cookies" are small text files a website can

use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's access to and use of the site and to track behavior of

the web pages you visit, among other uses. Our website may automatically collect Cookies and other

information, including, but not limited to, your domain name, and Energy Rewards may compile

aggregate data for statistical purposes to improve our content of our website or to better administer the

web pages available on the Energy Rewards website.

When and if Energy Rewards requests an email address from you, you will be given the opportunity to

indicate whether or not you wish to receive future email solicitations from us. Regardless, from time to

time we may send you emails for other reasons, including, but not limited to servicing your energy account

with us.

Privacy Questions

This website is owned and operated by Energy Rewards. This Privacy Policy is to provide you with

assurance and explain Energy Rewards' policy to ensure your personal information is protected and

properly used. If you have questions about this Policy, please contact us at 1-877-811-7023, 8:30 am to

6:30 pm, Eastern Standard Time.

Energy Rewards, LLC

535 Connecticut Avenue, 6th Floor

Norwalk, CT 06854

If you would like to know what information Energy Rewards retains or if you wish to have Energy Rewards

change your information because it is out of date or inaccurate, please contact us at 1-877-811-7023, 8:30

am to 6:30 pm, Eastern Standard Time and we will modify your record accordingly.

Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Energy Rewards reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy and its e‐mail practices at any time. If we

decide to make material changes to our policy regarding privacy and/or e‐mail practices, we will notify

you here, on our mobile Web site home page and on our Web site home page prior to the changes taking

effect, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what

circumstances, if any, we disclose it. When an update is made, the date at the top of this page changes

to reflect the date new content was posted. You may want to visit this Web site and mobile Web site

periodically to review the current Privacy Policy. Use of our Web site and mobile Web site after the

posting of a revised privacy policy constitutes your agreement with the revised policy. This Privacy Policy

is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party. Use of

this website and mobile Web site after the posting of a revised Privacy Statement constitutes your

acceptance of our privacy practices.

Copyright © Energy Rewards, LLC 2018
